





Summary

Jump to Section

An accomplished professional, with diversified experience as the Cross-Functional Technical Program Manager and delivery management functions with strong leadership, communication and technical excellence focusing on delivering results in terms of revenue generation & profitability

Enterprise wide standards driver with leadership abilities in setting up strategic goals, making decisions for the program establishing delivery governance and processes for the teams; experienced with Agile implementation and embraced, supported agility

Excellence in managing a multi-million dollars portfolio; consistently grew & augmented the bottom-line and top-line of key accounts

Work Experience

- SNITC as Technical Program Manager Nov 2018 to Till Date
- Accenture as IT Projects Delivery Manager Feb 2017 to Oct 2018
- Ultra Computer Services (UCS) as Technical Project Manager Jan 2016 to Jan 2017

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

^ Back to Ton

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from Madurai Kamaraj University (MKU) in 2015

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Jira, MS-Projects, Trello, Kanban	
My Wizard, Opera, Git	
Confluence, DevOps	

1

Important

Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

Jenkins, Ansible, Nexus, Sonar	
Dockers, Kubernetes	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Arabic				
Hindi				
English				
Tamil				
Telugu				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.